NO ANIMALS WERE HARMED DURING
THE FILMING OF THIS PRODUCTION
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com
Once upon a time...
... a sparrow...
... was yearning for food.
Later on...
... as the sparrow was desperately
searching for food ...
... it was getting closer and closer to
the trap of a hunter.
Poor sparrow...
...,just as it was about to be trapped,
was noticed by a hawk flying in the sky.
The hawk immediately descended...
... and caught the sparrow a second
before it went into trap.
However...
... later the hawk realized...
... it got into trap too.
The hawk then looked the hunter in the
eyes...
... and told him..
... ''Please have mercy on me.''
''You have everything you need.''
''We don't know each other.''
''I got into your trap reluctantly.''
''Just set me free.''
''Also''...
... ''Never I did something bad to you.''
The hunter...
... contemplated for a while...
... and then told the hawk...
...''What about the sparrow? Has it ever
done something bad to you?''
Then the hunter set the sparrow free...
... grabbed the hawk by its feet...
... and went on his way to the village.
Whether muslim or not...
... the sparrows of these lands are
entrusted to us.
We will make those inglorious dogs regret
everything they had done.
We are going to stick the arrow of justice
on their throats!
We have become sick of waiting for you!
So we armed ourselves and came here
to fight side by side with the Valiants.
Welcome.
You already brought joy, Hatuns.
The soldiers of Yarıhisar are strong
enough to defend their castle.
But...
... in order to defeat the Turks outside
the castle...
... we need support.
Don't we, Helen?
Yes, we do.
We need support to defend the Keşiş
Strait.
If they move together with the soldiers
of Bilecik's feudal lord...
... and fight together...
... along with the help of our soldiers...
... they will do more than just defending
the Keşiş Strait...
... in my opinion.
I will handle this issue, Nikola.
I'd be glad.
The door!
Bravo, Nikola!
Bravo.
Flatyos.
I wasn't expecting this.
Doesn't Osman want the same thing?
Killing you when you don't expect him.
Our assault shook Osman so bad that I'm
sure he can't find the way of his Tent.
Yes. We destroyed his dream of becoming
the Sultan of a state, Nikola.
But you know Osman.
He won't give up.
We always need to be careful.
The suffering of Osman gives me
power, Flatyos.
When he suffers, I constantly feel
reborn.
And just like you say, he is Osman
after all.
I'm sure he is planning his next move
right now.
I'm going to end him the moment he puts
his plan in action.
The support our emperor has sent will
arrive here soon.
We are going to struck them like a
thunderbolt, Flatyos.
It's me, Alexander!
Stop!
It's me.
Alexander, you fool!
I see these lands made you stronger,
my friend.
And your sense of art didn't soften you.
You fool!
Don't you know the crown on my head is
sacred?
Whatever we went through happened as to
fools like you!
When new one comes, the old one loses its
value, my friend.
Our emperor has declared you the new
lord of all feudal lords.
And this is...
... your new crown, my friend.
Congratulations, Nikola.
Where are my troops, Alexander?
I came first to make way, my friend.
I will bring your troops tomorrow when
it's more secure.
Then we will wait for your order to
attack the Turks.
Our dreams will soon come true, Mighty
Caesar.
So soon.
After he saw that child in Söğüt in such
a condition...
... he has started burn with the pursue
of revenge.
Inshallah, my Rab will grant us victory
soon.
Inshallah.
Otherwise, we can't cool off the anger
of my Bey.
Don't worry, Gonca Hatun.
No one can harm you when you are with us.
I brought you biscuits.
They will give you strength while
fighting.
They are for all of us, right?
Loony lad, he is.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
Bon appetit.
I heard you haven't had anything for days.
The moment I got in power...
... they tried to destroy my reputation.
If I don't get my revenge from them...
... we might never be taken serious
again, my Bala.
You are right, my Osman.
But remember that you never left a
misdeed unpunished.
I'm a Bey now.
They will enjoy even the smallest misdeed
done against me.
I'm sure they are willing to destroy my
reputation before I get stronger.
For sure, they know the Valiants of these
lands...
... will become one under the flag of
mine.
For this exact reason, they are trying
to take me down, my Bala.
I need to take my revenge before it is
too late.
They need to be filled with sorrow before
they even start to enjoy their victory.
And they must quiver in fear.
People must witness our victory first
so that...
... they can become one under our flag
as soon as possible.
Praise be upon my Valiant!
The Mongols destroyed the Seljuks.
And those who fled had to move closer
to the borders of Byzantine.
And now the Byzantine is attacking.
We are in between of two separate flames.
Maybe...
... if no voice becomes hope for our
people...
... if no flag of a new state flies in the
sky...
... and if our people lose their hope
in the end...
... we might even get disarrayed for good.
This is the sole reason of my fight.
Because of this, we can never back down.
A thousand thanks to my Rab, he made
me the lover of a such Valiant.
Thanks to my Rab, I was granted a
gazelle-eyed beauty who share my dreams.
He granted me a lover who is willing
suffer for this cause of mine.
My Bey.
I have news for you.
Troops who left Constantinople to help
Nikola will arrive at İnegöl tomorrow.
Oh, praise be!
Thanks to my Rab!
Allahu Akbar!
Let us come with you, Osman Bey.
May you go back to Tent and straighten
the affairs there, my Bala.
And send our regards to everyone.
The Emperor, Andronikos the third, with
this crown he sent...
... has declared his commander and
representative, noble Ayos Nikola,...
... from Inegol to Jordan, the feudal
landlord of all borders...
...in parallel with Turkish lands.
May our Holy Father grant many victories
to Ayos Nikola on his holy mission.
Amen!
My sacred friends.
My mighty soldiers!
We are face to face with the strongest
enemy...
... the Roman Empire has ever fought
against since its foundation!
Because of this reason, we need to stop
fighting with each other...
... and defeat our enemy by becoming one!
I, the Lord of all feudal landlords,
Ayos Nikola...
... will not disappoint our emperor!
And I promise you all that I will send the
Turks back to where they come from!
Alexander, leave this castle now...
... and come with the army that will
bring me victory.
Don't worry, Nikola. You will get your
army today.
Alexander, Turks are everywhere.
Keep your eyes wide open.
I always liked precautions.
They are the ones who need to be careful.
Feudal landlord, Nikola.
Your new crown suits you well, Nikola.
It's an honor to fight for you, Great
Commander.
The same applies to you, Flatyos.
Let me see it.
Okay, continue.
Thank you, Hatun
May you live long.
Bismillahirrahmanirrahim.
I'm always happy to help.
I hope it's for good, son.
Do you think it's unfair to work since you
are the son of a Bey?
Don't you forget that we are working for
the future of all Kayıs.
We are building this place so that they
will always...
... have a place to educate themselves.
Can't you face this fact?
I want to become an Alp and fight.
The world is full of Alps and soldiers.
However, the world lacks enlightened
scholars.
Do you know why?
Because without scholars, no state
can survive.
The future of a state depends on them.
And Kayı Tent needs those scholars
as well.
Father. I'm the only one who is aware of
the flame burning inside me.
I want to fight!
Uncle Gündüz!
Tell me, nephew.
Please back me up.
Can a muslim be told not to go fighting?
Of course not.
But you are still too young.
Hear me out for a second.
One needs to train for fighting.
And you, my beloved nephew, hold pen
instead of sword.
You are mistaken.
I read in the morning, and train at night.
Because I'm a Bey of Kayı.
The last thing he said is true, Savcı.
He is a Bey of Kayı.
And he is going to live his own fate.
He wants to be like his uncle Osman.
Oh, my brother.
Which young boy doesn't?
You are right, brother.
He and his Alps are nowhere to be found.
They are probably fighting.
-May Allah make their swords sharp.
-Amin
Let's go. We still have lots to do.
Come on, Alps! We need to be faster.
What's up, Master Davud?
It feels like you're not forging steel
this time.
Enough, Master Davut. For how long this
resentment going to last?
Answer to me.
Why did you favor Dündar Bey on the
election?
You shouldn't be surprised.
You know I want peace since the beginning.
Look what happened just because we
wanted to take İnegöl.
You are referring to the shahada of
Beys, İdris Bey.
You make insinuations by the blood of
our martyrs.
Know that I won't hesitate to hit you with
this hammer.
I belong to this Tent too, Davud Bey.
Of course I'm sad because of our martyrs
and Flatyos' escape.
I only wanted have heart-to-heart talk.
I'm offended.
Every blood droplet will be avenged.
Droplet by droplet, we are going to get
our revenge.
Just like this!
They are all going to be crushed!
Then, will be cooled down like this.
Inshallah.
Tell the soldiers to make themselves
presentable, Commander.
We need to look good for the presence of
feudal landlord Nikola.
As you order, my commander.
It's a trap! Get on your positions!
Defensive formation!
Don't scatter around!
It's a trap! Be careful!
Don't leave your positions!
They are up there!
Allahu Akbar!
Allah is eternal!
Thank you, my Rab.
Thank you.
I wish you ease, Hatuns.
Thank you, Selcen Hatun.
I hope it's for good, Hazal Hatun.
Indeed, it is.
I have been sewing and cooking non-stop
for days.
I'm as light as a bird now.
Oh, how magnificent.
But, can you elaborate more?
I'm doing these things to take my mind
off Dündar Bey.
You have every right to do these things.
Let Dündar worry about his own-self.
That's what I will do now.
Welcome, my daughter.
Thank you, Selcen mother.
Welcome, Bala Hatun.
Thank you, Hazal Hatun.
-I wish you ease.
-Thank you.
I have things to tell you.
-Follow me.
-Let's go.
I wish you ease, Hatuns.
Thank you, Bala Hatun.
May your hands don't see any trouble.
After you.
Now that Lena Hatun is here, I can start.
Hazal and Lena Hatun.
Teachers are going to be here soon to
teach our children how to read.
Hazal Hatun, I want you to fabricate the
tents.
And Lena Hatun, I want you to provide the
essential goods for them.
These are your duties.
Sure thing.
Sure thing, Bala Hatun.
No one but me can help you with these
things.
Don't worry, Bala Hatun.
I already made the preparations.
Perhaps, you can help us with installing
and furnishing the tents.
Of course.
From now on, only a single Hatun will be
responsible of the drinks.
And who she is shall not make anyone get
close to them.
As you order, Bala Hatun.
I need to go now.
-I wish you ease, Hatuns.
Thank you, Bala Hatun.
May everything be easy.
Now that her little tongue is used to
giving orders...
... may Allah help us from now on.
If it wasn't for your treason, we wouldn't
be hearing her orders.
Selamun Aleyküm.
Aleyküm Selam.
Welcome, Dündar Bey.
-To what do we owe the honor?
-Thank you.
I came to celebrate you.
Thanks for coming.
How is the business?
Is everything okay?
Thanks to Osman Bey, we managed to find
a workshop so quickly.
May you be worthy of him.
I see lots of goods.
It's not so easy to bring goods all the
way from Aleppo to here as to Mongols.
There is always a key that can open all
doors.
Do you mean being a successful merchant?
I appreciate it.
We also heard about you being an expert
merchant, my Bey.
I was once a merchant but now-
It's easy to be the wolf of mountains.
However, I can't tell the same thing about
being the wolf of trade.
No one is better than you when it comes
to commerce.
And it'd be an honor to make business with
you.
Thank you.
You have a smart assistant, merchant
Melih.
Not everyone can find an assistant like
him.
Süleyman is like a son to me.
Dündar Bey, I have been waiting for you to
talk about an opportunity.
I'm listening.
My caravan from Konya will arrive
here soon.
If I can sell the goods that I bought from
the Indian lands in Byzantine cities...
... I will make a huge profit.
And you need a partner who you can trust.
You are right.
Being trustworthy alone is not enough.
We need a Bey who can make peace with
the thereabout feudal landlords.
What's your offer?
Oh, people!
I have news.
I hope it's for good.
People, I have news!
Listen to me carefully, folks.
Open your ears for me.
The revenge of Hasan, İlyas, Fazıl, and
Turan Bey has been taken!
A large army of heathens got ambushed
by Osman Bey near İnegöl...
... and got completely destroyed.
May you live long Osman Bey!
That heathen called Nikola is defeated
once again...
... and the soldiers of Islam are
victorious!
May Allah always help our Osman Bey.
He put a smile on our faces once again.
What's your offer?
Half-and-half, Dündar Bey.
I accept it.
Let's do some business.
Did you see Dündar's face?
I think he didn't like the news.
If you were him, would you like the
victory of your enemy, Simon?
We'll get stronger in the Tent if we
control Dündar.
And we will get the papers we are looking
for in a short time.
The time Holy Father gave us is about
to expire.
May God be with us.
The horse of my father doesn't have a
owner now.
Just like us, it has no one, my son.
They showed no mercy on our mountain-like
Valiant.
Osman Bey promised to get our
revenge, mother.
I believe, he will avenge my father's
death.
Mother!
Just like I told you, he came back!
Welcome, my Bey!
I'm sorry for your loss.
May he rest in heaven.
Thank you, my Bey.
When I heard you summoned him, I prayed
for him to fight against the heathens.
I'm sad because he died before
fighting, my Bey.
My sister.
How lucky you are to be a wife of a
martyr.
Inshallah, you will meet in heaven once
again.
However, Ali promised me something.
He is going to grow up.
And rule his Tent.
After that, we are going to fight side by
side.
And Osman Bey promised that he would
take the revenge of my father's death.
It's already taken, Ali Bey.
With the help of Allah, we became
victorious.
The heathens got defeated harsly.
We made a hill with their heads.
We crushed them so bad that...
Our revenge has been taken.
Inside these chests are the golds we
acquired from the heathens.
They belong to Ali Bey now.
May Allah bless you, my Bey.
May he bless you too.
Bring me the horse of Hasan Bey.
May you saddle it up.
My Ali Bey.
It is entrusted to you now.
Don't you ever worry about your age.
Because, the Sultan of Seljuks, Çağrı
Bey, got sick one day.
And declared his son, Alparslan, a
commander when he was only ten years old.
And our Sultan Alparslan won his first
battle when he was only ten.
My beloved people, our children grow
up with duties and gain foresights.
Because of this, the Bey of this Tent will
be Ali Bey.
You shall all pay homage to him.
From now on, he will be my ears and
eyes in charge of these lands.
He who harms him will harm me too.
His enemies will be my enemies too.
May you all comprehend this well.
I, son of Hasan Gazi, Ali Bey!
From now on, I hold the sword of battles!
Allahu Akbar!
May you live long, Ali Bey!
The hardest part of being a sculptor
is sculpting yourself, Flatyos.
Sculpting yourself is basically
recreating your own-self.
I see you're happy, Nikola.
How can I be not happy?
The emperor made me the lord of
all feudal landlords.
He sent me a new crown.
And my troops are coming.
Of course I'll be happy.
I'm sure you will rule the whole
Rome soon, Nikola.
Don't worry, Flatyos.
When that day comes, you will be
standing next to me.
But first...
... with my new troops, I will make
the Turks...
... regret coming to these lands.
My sir, the support troops got attacked
by Kayıs on their way to İnegöl.
The soldiers are dead.
And Commander Alexander is injured.
Osman...
You...
...you killed my soldiers!
He killed my soldiers!
Osman...
Did he kill my soldiers?
Osman! Did he disband my
unit?
My soldiers, huh?
My unit?
We will fight, Osman. I will
rip you apart.
I will bury every part of you
in a different place.
The beys that you trust so much...
...the alps that you trust so much...
...won't find a piece of you.
I promise you, they won't!
They won't!
I promise you! I promise you!
I promise you!
Alps!
Kayı Tribe is under the protection
of Ertuğrul Ghazi's son Osman Bey.
Ensheathe.
Step forward.
Mashallah.
Long live Osman Bey!
Thank Allah for...
...granting us this victory.
My ghazis...
...ones who deserve it,
should take their shares.
And the people of Kayı should
get their shares too.
My altruistic and valiant mujahids.
From now on...
...we'll run to one battle after another,
one victory after another.
For this reason, we won't relax...
...we won't stop...
...we won't get tired,
we won't run away.
We will always be together.
We'll banish the hypocrites.
And we'll do our job...
...with love.
From now, we will fight...
...and Allah will give
us victory.
Long live Osman Bey!
Alps, hand out the spoils.
Bring my share inside.
What did I tell you?
I told you that Turks are everywhere!
I told you to open your eyes!
I told you to be cautious!
How did they come out of nowhere, Nikola?
They came like ghosts.
We didn't know what to do. All my
soldiers died by their hands.
Alexander, you are an honorable
and a great warrior.
I know this but the thing is...
...being a great warrior...
...isn't enough.
We need more.
You, Flatyos,
invite all the lords...
...that the Emperor gives orders.
I, the lord of lords...
...Nikola, will form a great
crusader army...
...against Turks!
Then, I will behead every Turk
in these lands.
May Allah bless our fallen soldiers.
She is stubborn.
She doesn't milk.
-Maybe you are failing.
-Come and do it then.
-I won't. It's a woman's job.
-Then don't speak as you know it.
What if I do it?
Are you up for a horse race?
-What are you doing, Gonca Hatun?
-You lost on purpose, didn't you?
You did that, Gonca Hatun.
What did I do?
Gonca Hatun, do you really say that you
couldn't milk that goat?
Or did you act to make
me help you?
-How did you know?
-I saw you milking that goat.
When?
I couldn't sleep that night.
Morning's lights were on Ertuğrul
Bey's tent.
-There was hoarfrost, right?
-There was, Gonca Hatun.
And there was a hard
morning frost.
It was so cold. I wanted to
drink milk and get warm.
When I saw you, I couldn't go
anywhere. I was stunned.
Why?
I wanted to get warm.
But...
-But?
-But I didn't want to get burned.
That's what happened.
-Did you control the plates?
-We did, Bala Hatun.
Good.
Bring the bread warm.
Same for the meal.
As you command, Bala Hatun.
More power to you, women!
Gonca.
What's up?
You are smiling.
Bala, finally, Boran Alp has spoken.
My pretty sister.
I'm so glad. Inshallah you will always
be happy.
Inshallah. Thank you, my good sister
Thank you.
You should act quick, Gonca.
Bala, where is Osman Bey?
When will he come?
I wonder that too, Gonca.
After the spoils got shared,
he vanished.
May your victory last forever, Osman Bey.
But I wish you had seen us as well.
Oh my Allah. How much
do you love your Osman that...
...you don't even let me be
mad at him?
-I'm so hungry.
-Come, my child, come. Look!
-Here.
-You told me that my father is an angel.
He must've brought them, right?
It's our state, son.
My Allah, you heard my cryings.
Thak you.
Boran Alp, where is Osman Bey?
I was out of the tribe for something.
Nobody knows.
-Don't you know, Bala Hatun?
-I don't know either, Savcı brother.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
Mashallah. Our dinner table is
fruitful again.
Go on.
My bey, you were missing.
It's a secret of the bey, Bala.
We can't reveal everything.
With the name of Allah.
Here you go.
-What do you think you are doing?
-Should Cerkutay be hungry?
You can't eat from the boiler!
Did you come down from
a mountain?
Look at me!
Do you know who I am?
Aren't you Aygül?
What are you saying?
You... When did you take it?
Give it back to me!
I'm Cerkutay. I steal things like
this. I don't like to eat what I'm given.
I like to take from other people.
Are you proud of it?
I didn't live in the mountains
but in forests.
I grew up with weasels.
Bear!
Are you mad that I called
you crazy?
If I see you acting like
a weasel again...
...I'll cut your hand.
Remember that.
She is a tough woman.
I congratulate your victory, Osman Bey.
It's a great victory.
It brought glory.
Allah has the real glory.
Allah.
Thank you, uncle.
I congratulate your victory, Osman Bey.
May it last forever.
Thank you too, brother.
-It's because of your good prayers.
-Thank you.
Now, the sword of Jihad is on the
hand of the worthy one.
No one can doubt that.
From now, my brother Savcı is the
scholar and...
...the light of science.
And no one can doubt that.
Thank you, brother.
Thank you.
But without telling you...
...my brother Gündüz and I
started giving lessons for our children.
What a great idea, brother.
No permission is needed for
something so good.
You've done me a favor.
May Allah bless you.
Thank you, brother.
Now, no one can break our unity.
-We should keep our love.
-Amin.
No one can make us forget
that we are brothers...
...that we are of the same blood.
-Amin.
Amin.
Savcı Bey.
-What is the foundation of a state?
-It's family, Osman Bey. Family.
-How can a nation ascend?
-By raising with responsibility...
...morals and honor from the
family.
By learning sharing and helping.
For this reason, family is holy.
Family is sacred.
My brother Boran...
...and my sister Gonca...
...want to marry.
Mashallah. Mashallah.
And I think that it will bring
good.
We should be quick on such
good things.
Now, we'll both fight and
gather a wedding feast!
Boran brother...
...play your qopuz.
-As you order, my bey.
-Thank you.
With the name of Allah.
When you became 20...
...you have seen the dream.
Against the all tyrants...
...Osman Bey stands
like a wall.
Haji Edebali's follower...
...may the towers of the
heathens get demolished.
Ertuğrul Ghazi's pride...
...Osman Bey is a different valiant.
He subdued many people...
...he fought valiantly.
He strikes the tyrants
with his claws...
...Osman Bey is like a
dark wolf.
He strikes the tyrants
with his claws...
...Osman Bey is like a
dark wolf.
On good horses with
grey mane hairs...
...with good armors and
sharp weapons...
...with steel-hearted valiant
alps.
Osman Bey writes a saga.
When the innocents cried...
...the earth shake.
Appeared a hero...
...like a magnificent tent,
Osman Bey.
He subdued many people.
He fought valiantly.
He strikes the tyrants
with his claws.
Osman Bey is like a dark wolf.
He strikes the tyrants
with his claws.
Osman Bey is like a dark wolf.
With the name of Allah.
My bey, what is this salaat
you do?
The salaat we do is gratitude,
Cerkutay.
It's begging. It's remembering
our Allah.
Being in Allah's presence.
We beg to Tengri.
But we don't know Muhammad.
May he rest in peace.
Even Osman Bey turns weird
when he hears that name.
Why is that?
Because Cerkutay, he is the sultan
of both worlds.
Is he so rich?
Some nights, he would sleep
hungry...
...he would repair his own
sweater...
...he would eat a crumble of
betel nut.
Why do you call him a sultan?
He doesn't have anything.
-He can't even solve his hunger.
-Not because he is poor, Cerkutay.
Because of his throne.
His throne.
Cerkutay, the real sultanete
is in the hearts of people.
The real sultan is the one who reigns
in hearts.
And, Cerkutay,
the real conquest...
...is the conquest
of hearts.
That's the kind of sultan he was.
He was merciful,
he was thoughtful...
...he was concerned about his
ummah.
And Cerkutay, he loves children.
Children?
Yes.
Tell me, Cerkutay.
Do you love Muhammad?
I...
Does he love me?
Cerkutay did horrible things.
Cerkutay killed people...
...Cerkutay killed children.
Weasels taught Cerkutay, my bey.
Weasels taught Cerkutay.
Wait, wait, wait.
Hold on, my boy.
Calm down.
Calm down, my son.
My bey, he doesn't love me, does he?
Cerkutay.
We will swear off.
We will beg.
We will cry like this.
We will love children.
We will love women.
We will love trees, the animals.
Everything the god created.
So, he will love us too.
In the other world, he will invite
us to his banner.
Even me?
Even you, Cerkutay.
Even you.
So, what do you think?
How will we improve Söğüt's trade?
From Çobanoğulları
to Germiyanoğulları...
...from Nikea to Prusa,
I have important connections.
If we manage to bring enough
goods to Söğüt...
...after a while, all the merchants
will come here.
Is it easy to bring that much goods,
Dündar Bey?
You know that the road
from Halep to here...
...is very dangerous.
Mongols and bandits are
getting taxes.
What's your solution?
Just like your late father
has done before...
...only you can save
our caravans...
...from them, my bey.
As long as you have such a helper,
I don't doubt how you'll sell your goods.
-He knows what to say.
-Thank you, my bey.
Süleyman is like a son to me.
I've listened to what you've said.
You have my permission
for this.
Kayı alps will protect your caravans.
Your goods will come to Söğüt safely.
Uncle! As a Kayı bey...
...improving the trade
is your duty.
Now their goods are under our
protection...
...if something happens, it's our
duty to pay compensation.
Thank you.
Now...
...my expectation from you is...
When people hear the name Söğüt...
...they'll think of justice, honesty
and security.
Every merchant will think that...
...their goods will be best regarded
in Söğüt.
This is my expectation from you.
-Speak now, uncle.
-If you give me this responsibility...
...I want to revive Söğüt.
We made our first agreement.
May it be good.
Uncle, you will have this duty.
It's your responsibility to revive
Söğüt.
May it be good.
You can talk to each other for the rest.
Thank you.
My bey, it's not my place but...
You wonder if I trust Dündar Bey,
Boran.
My intentions are good.
I gave him another opportunity now.
You should give opportunity and
responsibility to gain their loyalty.
Thank you, my bey.
Form the greatest caravan around here.
I will tell my brother-in-law
Yavlak Arslan too...
...we'll sell goods to Çobanoğlu
market as well.
It'll bring me luck to make business
with a trader like you, Dündar Bey.
We have luck and our way is clear.
Let us begin,
then we'll grow together.
-Come, let us go to my tent.
-Thank you, Dündar Bey.
-We want to visit Bamsı Bey.
-All right.
From now, we are partners.
We'll be seeing each other a lot.
He might've hidden it in his tent.
It seems that it'll be difficult.
We entered Osman's tribe...
...if needed, we'll enter his tent
as well.
-How so?
-Dündar opened the door for us.
Bamsı will take us in.
Let's go and talk to Bamsı Bey...
...about the good old days.
Osman gave you the duty to
keep you on his side.
I'll make him profit a lot, wife.
A lot.
He'll have much more trust
in me.
He'll love his uncle a lot.
I'll strangle him with the
bow string he used.
He'll ask for mercy,
he'll ask me to forgive him.
That day, you won't forgive him,
Dündar Bey.
His annoying wife gave orders
to everyone today.
She gave me, the only daughter
of Çobanoğullar...
...an order.
That moment, I felt like I was under
a boulder.
Just for you...
...I was patient. Just for you.
My beautiful wife.
Stay calm.
We'll ask them for what they've
done to us.
-Inshallah.
-We will.
-May I enter, Dündar Bey?
-Brother?
Come, Yavlak Arslan.
-Brother!
-Sister.
-Salam Alaikum.
-Alaikum Salam.
Alaikum Salam.
What's wrong, Yavlak Arslan?
What brought you here at night?
I was hunting at night.
A gazelle brought me here.
Sertaç warned me to not enter
Osman's tents but...
...I wanted to see my sister.
-Welcome, brother. Welcome.
Come. Not at all. This is your
tent as well.
So, it's been a long while.
Osman became a bey.
And you lost all your duties, is that so?
Yes, but you...
...became Osman's ally.
-Yes, I have.
Thank you.
How did you do that, brother?
Osman Bey is shrewd, a good warrior...
...he is a smart man. Only he could
watch my back against Geyhatu.
He should stop Byzantine here
and I will kick Geyhatu out of here.
These lands will be the home of
Islam and Turks again.
-Inshallah.
Brother, you should stay here tonight.
Be our guest.
The night is long.
We can talk.
We have things to tell you
as well.
My bey, what is this?
It's our flag.
A new flag?
-Wouldn't the beys object?
-They wouldn't.
They won't.
Because...
...this flag has a meaning...
...it's for the Islam world.
Inshallah, we'll be the hope of
the whole Islam world.
Inshallah.
From a tribe to beylic, and
from there to the whole world...
...we will spread out.
Bala.
-Give this to the women.
-As you order, my bey.
My bey, you handed out your
share, didn't you?
Thank Allah.
-No one knows, right?
-What did our prophet say?
One hand shouldn't see the other's
charity.
When it's seen by people, it's not charity
but tyranny to the one taking the help.
And since I'm the bey, it's
my responsibility.
Mashallah, my bey.
Bala.
-Yes, my bey.
-I love your pretty eyes.
Father!
Son.
My will.
My will, Osman.
Father...
Osman?
Bala...
My father...
...left a will before dying.
He wants me to have a new wife.
It's my father's will.
I will do it.
I will have a new wife.
It's true now.
I wanted you to know.
Horsefeathers to you, Osman.
Why didn't you tell me all this time?
I couldn't hit a gazelle like you,
looking directly into your eyes.
Not at all, Osman.
Haven't I told you to have
a new wife?
See, our Ertuğrul Bey ordered it.
There is no return now.
It's your father's will.
It's your bey's will.
You will do it.
Don't cry.
No, Osman.
If you cry, you will make us suffer.
I won't cry.
I won't rebel. I'll be patient.
This is our fate, Osman.
This is our fate.
O' the throne!
What do you want from me?
How hard is it to sit on you?
O' the throne!
You don't accept two beys on you.
You don't share me with
anyone.
O' the fur, you say the future of Kayı...
...but you make me threaten...
...even my most beloved ones.
O' the throne!
You say the stability,
the future...
...children...
...but...
...you give sorrow to...
...the person...
...I love the most.
My heart and soul...
...my love.
You throw her to dungeons...
...with my hands and words.
My Allah...
...don't leave me alone.
Don't leave me alone, my Allah.
On this difficult mission...
...don't make me one of those
who lost their ways.
Keep me on our prophet's
path always.
Give me true friends.
Keep me on your path always.
Keep me.
Osman Bey!
May I enter?
Come in.
They said that Osman Bey ascended
to the throne, so I came with a gift.
But it seems, the throne is
on the shoulders of Osman Bey.
My burden is heavy.
-What is its secret?
-You shouldn't ask me...
...but to this wood that turned
into this shape, bey's son.
Forgive me, Osman Bey.
-You honored my tent.
-Not at all.
Not at all.
Come.
With the name of Allah.
It's very huge.
Thank Allah. Thank Allah.
Thank Allah, Osman Bey.
Thank Allah.
How many people can have
such a big tent nowadays?
If you accept it...
...I want to give you a gift,
Osman Bey.
It's a dervish accessory.
You put it on your neck.
Give it to me.
Like this.
What does it do?
To beg, Osman Bey.
To beg.
Dervish doesn't ask for from anyone
but Allah.
But this two-headed dragon...
Our desires...
Dervishes wear this to tame
their desires.
And go into life...
...and you start to
travel the world.
The people once you had to compete
for the earthly goods, laugh at you.
They pity you.
And every laugh is cost you.
Some leave a gold...
...some leave food.
Some leave trash.
Every day, every gold...
...destroys the idol that you
built with your desires.
The days pass and this becomes
your closest friend.
And when you destroy your
idols...
...this becomes your crown.
You start to see the world
with different eyes.
Then, the world shows you
its secrets.
Osman Bey.
Osman the Dark, the hope of...
...all Turkmens, the Islam world...
...mothers, fathers, sons, daughters
even children, and dervishes!
Not at all.
This has been my comrade
for years.
Now it's yours.
You are a great bey.
Don't say that what will I do with it.
It's a metaphor. Understand it.
If you want to demolish the idol
that says...
... ''I'm a bey, I know everything''
you should beg like a dervish.
What will I beg for?
The thing that makes you a bey.
You should beg for knowledge
from the experts.
You should gather all those
who know, in this tent.
You should leave everything to
the one who know it.
Best scholars, talented artists,
good warriors...
...should gather in this tent.
Osman Bey.
Bey! You are a bey now.
The wolf on the mountain,
the sheep in the herd...
...the wind that blows, the bird
in the sky are under your protection.
How can you be strong enough?
How can you have that much time?
The knowledge that you
save in this...
...the people you save in this
will solve your problems.
Then, this throne won't
be on your shoulders.
You will sit on it.
Then, this tent will be the
center of the world.
And it will bring justice to
all living.
And your lineage will be known
as Osmans (Ottomans).
Osmans (Ottomans).
Ottomans! Ottomans!
Ottomans!
Allahu Akbar!
Please contact us for any inquiries
turkision@gmail.com